import 'package:quiz_app_tutorial/models/question.dart';

List<Question> python_questions = [
  Question(
    question: 'Q. All keywords in Python are in _________',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      ' Capitalized',
      ' lower case',
      ' UPPER CASE',
      ' None of the mentioned',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. What will be the value of the following Python expression? '
        '                 4 + 3 % 5',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      ' 7',
      ' 2',
      ' 4',
      ' 1',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q.  Which of the following is used to define a block of code in Python language?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      ' Indentation',
      ' Key',
      ' Brackets',
      ' All of the mentioned',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q.  Which keyword is used for function in Python language?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      ' Function',
      ' def',
      ' Fun',
      ' Define',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. Which of the following character is used to give single-line comments in Python?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      ' //',
      ' #',
      ' !',
      ' /*',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. Which of the following functions can help us to find the version of python that we are currently working on?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      ' sys.version(1)',
      ' sys.version(0)',
      ' sys.version()',
      ' sys.version',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. What is the order of precedence in python?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      ' Exponential, Parentheses, Multiplication, Division, Addition, Subtraction',
      ' Exponential, Parentheses, Division, Multiplication, Addition, Subtraction',
      ' Parentheses, Exponential, Multiplication, Division, Subtraction, Addition',
      ' Parentheses, Exponential, Multiplication, Division, Addition, Subtraction',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. Python supports the creation of anonymous functions at runtime, using a construct called __________',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      ' pi',
      ' anonymous',
      ' lambda',
      ' none of the mentioned',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
    'Q. What will be the output of the following Python code snippet if x=1?'
        'x<<2',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      ' 4',
      ' 2',
      ' 1',
      ' 8',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
    'Q. Which of the following is true for variable names in Python?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      ' underscore and ampersand are the only two special characters allowed',
      ' unlimited length',
      ' all private members must have leading and trailing underscores',
      ' none of the mentioned',
    ],
  ),
];
